You've grown.
How many centimeters are there?
Let's cut it off.
When do you decide to cut it?
You're right.
It's difficult.
A hand width of about a centimeter from the chin.
That's better.
I can't tell the difference.
But doesn't it look like a bob?
Yes, and I end up looking like this.
I think it's better like this.
Master's bob with an outside hook.
Is that a popular hairstyle?
Is it popular?
It's popular with girls. I'm talking about girls. What about me?
I don't know if the master's bob with the sweeping parted hairline is popular.
Is it cool? Here we go.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. You looked great.
You really had a mature look, didn't you?
The theme was "mature".
Like a chair or something.
A high chair.
Like this.
When the master gave a thump, the artist's picture fell off.
You know...
Me too.
I'm going to fall a lot this week.
It's the day it falls.
Is it a curse? Maybe it's a curse.
Is it Ellen Geiger's curse?
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's get on with the show.
Please let's get on with the show.
So, here we are.
Today is the 18th of January.
January 18th.
January 18th!
Yay!
Isn't it a little bit like that?
Yes, it is, isn't it? November 18th is a special day.
Really?
Yes, sir. It's the 118th.
Number 118?
You don't know the number 118? 118? I guess that's why we have this day.
Actually, isn't the number 110 or 119 famous? Yes, they are.
Actually, there's also a number 118, which is used by the Coast Guard as an emergency number.
In other words, they ask people to use 118 to report accidents on the sea, such as water accidents.
I've never heard of it before.
I didn't know there was such a thing. 118. When something happens at sea, you call 118.
I see. This is quite important, isn't it?
And it's only been in effect since 2011, so it's a recent thing.
Recently? Recently? Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well...
Well, let's see...
Let's go.
A quote.... from Momoebi Naoki.
Chofu City, Tokyo... thank you.
I'm studying... studying... studying... studying...
Thank you very much!
Takeshi Umizo or Ken Umizo, I don't think you know him from 2.
He was a novelist who passed away in 1989.
Anyway, what's so great about him is that he was a novelist.
Well, of course, he had one, and he actively went out.
And then...
My hobby is fishing, and I went to the Amazon in Brazil and went up a huge slope.
She caught a huge hill fish, and she won the Zos novel.
There's a famous novel called "Opa", about a Brazilian man named Opa.
When he was surprised, he said, "Are you serious?
I think it's a little bit like "Oh, Pa"...
He was a novelist and an outdoorsman, and even back then, he was actively involved in camping and other activities even before it became a part of the Japanese culture.
That person...
I said, "Don't be afraid of waste, and don't despise waste.
You don't know what's waste and what's not, Oppa.
Oh, yes, I understand very well.
When I was in my twenties, I thought it was all a waste of time, and I thought to myself, "How can my life be such a waste of time?
I felt like such a waste. I still feel like a waste a lot.
Yes, you're right.
I was waiting for a response, so I waited for them all, but they didn't seem to come, so I went myself.
So, you know, especially when I was in my teens or twenties, when I was really into something, I thought, "This isn't a waste of time.
I'm sure there were times, especially in my teens and twenties, when I thought, "This isn't a waste of time.
But I can tell you from my own experience that it wasn't a waste of time at all.
I made all kinds of stupid things.
When I was in my 20s, I was completely confused.
I went to the Tama River, you know, in the middle of the day with a piece of construction paper, and I was drawing pictures.
I was like a schoolboy, drawing pictures of the river and stuff.
And then he would come home at sunset.
He was called the Kiyoshi Yamashita of the Heisei era, right?
For real.
I didn't want to work, I didn't want to be anything at all, I was just kind of flustered and I didn't know what I wanted to be.
So-called "NEET".
That's right.
I wasn't a hermit, but I went to my friend's house at night and played Street Fighter 2.
Street Fighter 2.
I was playing Street Fighter 2, Street Fighter 2, Street Fighter 2, Street Fighter 2.
I was kind of a hermit.
I see.
And then my friend, who was my only friend at the time, told me that I was going to be ruined and that I needed to get out of the house, so he forced me to go out and start working part-time.
Heh.
So I started working outside the house, and that was fun.
I started to work outside the house, and I started to enjoy it again.
I was really good at drawing, and I put aside the question of whether I was good or bad at it, but I really came to like drawing.
I thought it was a waste of time, but at the time I really thought it was a waste of time, so I thought, "Oh really, I'll never get a job," and I thought, "I'm screwed.
My mom would get mad at me every night, and we'd fight every night about how mad she got at me, and I'd say, "Oh, yeah, where are you?
I'm sure my mom knows where I went to middle school, so I'm sure she went to middle school in Nagano Prefecture.
I'm sure she's in her twenties, so I'm sure she's in her twenties, so I'm sure she's in her twenties, so I'm sure she's in her twenties, but if it was a while ago...
If it was before... like in horror cartoons... or asses...
A lot of goods
2 Noodle Around Foot Noodle Around Foot Noodle Around Foot Noodle Around Foot Noodle Around Foot Noodle Around Foot Noodle Around Foot Noodle Around
I'm interested.
Boo-boo sound
Boo-boo-ong
Quindi
I said this yesterday when I was allowed to go to a birthday party.
I said this in front of the audience, "I want to sing a song about a character I've been really in love with lately, and I want to send my love to her, just like how I feel.
I want to send my love to you all.
I thought, "What's with this space?
I said, "Well, I'm so happy for you..." "Yes, I know, but that's exactly why I like games.
But sometimes I feel that if I'm going to play games, I could be doing something else.
But in my mind it's a relaxation and I do it because I like it so much.
I'll try to get better at it, maybe I can use it for something.
So maybe, as you get older and mature, you can really, you know...
I think there will come a time when it's not fashionable to do that kind of thing at work.
But it's not allowed, and I think it's better not to do that in a normal job.
That's right... when you're young... you should take in everything you're interested in.
I'm sure you'll be able to make the most of the hot water you're given.
I wish I could get in a time machine and tell myself back then that I wasn't wrong, because I thought I was wrong.
I thought I was wrong, so I'm sure I'm right.
I'm talking about Sotoku who just did it!
I'm talking about Takarotoku, not Takuya, not really a company, just a line of goods companies are over, Arthur...
I've got nothing to say, so let's talk about games... when I was young... there were rules about how many hours a day you shouldn't play games, of course...
But now it's a little bit different.
I can understand why parents want their children to play games all the time.
But the times are changing, and so are the professions, and the prestigious companies we used to think were great...
The kind of prestigious companies we used to think of are not so prestigious now.
Various things have changed.
That's right.
So I think things will change even more in the next 10 to 20 years.
You never know what's going to happen.
Let's do our best.
Oh!
ح ". I got up on the Takeda opening platform.
Why are you idiots in such a bad mood?
Burn newer, I'm off to the wrestling match!
I'll see you in a couple of hours.
So, I've got an announcement to make.
I've got an announcement to make, folks... an announcement about the Okanai Devil's Ball.
I've already announced it last time, but the VIP seats for the Odate Nai Devil are reserved seats S, which are right at the front of the line.
VIP seat S, the one at the very front of the line...
We've received a lot of reservations.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to your support, we've closed it up now.
We are not at the front of the line today, but...
It's not the front of the line, but it's the front of the line.
In the front.
VIP seats.
We'll start accepting applications from 8:00 a.m.
So please come on in.
By the way...
It's very popular.
It's hard to say "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh", "sacosh".
If it was a zakosh, it would be different, so we'll replace the zakosh with a zakosh as a souvenir for the VIPs.
I'd like you to apply for it again.
This "Sakosh" is a small shoulder bag.
A little shoulder bag.
That's right.
Is it okay?
But there are a lot of people who want it.
I guess the VIP S class got a throw-in today.
And some of them didn't get it.
Some people said they won.
That's the end of the game.
That's right.
Why not?
Give up... give up on the "S".
Maybe there won't be any more.
The game's over... sorry!
Sorry, Dr. Fanzai! I used the wrong word.
But you know... that means VIP will start accepting applications again today.
It's right in front of you.
Are you about this close?
If you want, you can see it from the corner of your eye.
Well, yesterday, at the birthday party, one of the things that stuck out in my mind was that I was shaking my head and saying, "I'm trying to respond to you, but you don't seem to respond at all.
They didn't respond.
It was funny to see him get angry.
For example, when I wave my hand, they wave back. If you wave your hand, they wave back. I'm doing it, but they say I'm not doing it.
Only at times like that do they look at other girls.
Since all the Ebitu-chan are in Odate, I'm sure a lot of these things happen.
I don't know what to look for.
So, I hope you'll join us!
Now, there is one more special offer today.
You had a birthday, didn't you, Mr. Mayama?
Yes, on the air.
That's why I'm going to present you with a present as usual.
I turned 27 years old
One month ago
I'm so happy!
It's huge!
Really?
HUGE!
What the heck is this?
It's an Opa like Ken Kaikou said.
Opa!
Here you go!
Wow!
What's this? That's a prediction stick!
The prediction stick! The famous!
The famous one that's rumored to ruin people... It's huge!
It's half the size of Maya Maya! What the hell! It is!
Wow! Wow!
Wow! Wow! It's so Christmassy! It's Christmassy!
Just like this place! Just like this! It's big! It's huge!
Can I open it? Go ahead! Thank you!
I'm so happy! We have a devil's charge! Happy Birthday, Tamamin! Thank you!
I had a birthday last year! Yes!
Yes! Aah! What is it? What is it?
Ah! What! What's this? Oh! That's amazing! What!
What is this? What! What! What! What is that?
A pillow? Not here! With the pillow? Yes!
Oh! So this is a pillow! An arm pillow and an arm pillow? Arms? Oh! Put it in like this! A pillow that you can knit and sleep on. I see!
Like that, so you can lie on your face. I see! I see! The kind you can use on a flight or something. That's great! On airplanes! On airplanes! Necklaces! Good! Pillow?
Do you still have it? What?
Travel pillow! And? What? Wait, you still have it? What? What?
What? Yes! What's this? Debris charge from Mr. Dedon Mori! Ah! Thank you! Congratulations! I'll take that as a yes,
What? What is it? Oh! Nice slippers and, uh!
Wow! Wow! Thank you! Cute! A cat! And then there's this,
Uh, candles! Oh! They even have candles? It's a snow hat! Wow!
Wow! Thank you! Wow! Wow! Thank you!
No, but, yeah. I'm home alone right now, burning candles and stuff,
No, I'm burning them! Burn it! Like this, like this, like this. I'll burn it! No, I mean..,
Like this? No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! Are you okay? Are you, uh... are you calling something or something?
Magic circle! Like a magic circle! I didn't pull any magic circle! I didn't! I didn't do the ritual! Yes, yes, yes!
Hey! I like this! Oh! I like this! I love it! Thank you!
You know, you can borrow them on airplanes and stuff, right? Yes, that's right. It's so comfortable!
Does it come with an eye mask? What? What? I can't sleep unless it's dark! That's great! Thank you!
Wow! I'm so happy! Thank you! Yes, yes, yes, yes!
We also received one from Tamaro! Thank you!
Thank you very much! Wow, I love it! Comfortable! Wow! Comfy!
But it looks kind of lifesaving! Something fell off my neck!
Man! Man! Like a person!
What the hell? Are we looking at some kind of clunker robot? I'm looking at a clunker robot, oh, my God!
Oh! Watch out! Watch out! Hey!
Like Wogman! Oh, thank you! Thank you very much!
Well, well, well, well... Yes! Yes! Thank you!
Well, I think it's time to call it a night, so we'll see you next week, or is there no next week?
No next week? Until New Year's Eve on the 31st?
Until New Year's Eve! Until New Year's Eve! Oh! See you on New Year's Eve! That's what I mean!
Yes! Was it 11:30? Yes!
Yes! Yes! I'd like to see you at night! Yes!
Yes! So, see you on New Year's Eve! See you on New Year's Eve!
Okay, I'm done.